[
    {
        "question": "What magic does Tenebris use?",
        "answer": ["Medium Charge", "Midsphere", "medium charge", "midsphere"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it possible to shock bosses?",
        "answer": ["No", "no"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many acts are there in the main storyline of Shadow Fight 2?",
        "answer": ["7", "seven"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the chest from which you can get the Set for 5000 shards?",
        "answer": ["Chest Of Heavenly Steel", "chest of heavenly steel"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What weapons does Flauros use?",
        "answer": ["Power Fists", "power fists"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Weapon used by Architect?",
        "answer": ["Two Handed Hammer", "two handed hammer", "Don't cross the directior"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the alternate name of the resurrection set?",
        "answer": ["revive", "revival", "Revival", "Revive"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What enchantment allows you to copy your opponent's magic?",
        "answer": ["plot twist"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Shadow's assistant in Act 7?",
        "answer": ["Kali"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most used medium enchantment on a private server?",
        "answer": ["frenzy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What weapon does Trickster give to Shadow?",
        "answer": ["nunchacku"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many seconds does a raid battle last?",
        "answer": ["45"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many mercenaries attack the Shadow in Act 6?",
        "answer": ["5"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was SF2 released?",
        "answer": ["2013"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which weapon does Shin use?",
        "answer": ["Kunai"]
    },
    {
        "question": " Which weapon does Karcer use?",
        "answer": ["Hunger Sickles"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which weapon has super slash with more than 5 hits?",
        "answer": ["Sabers", "Krises", "Mowers", "Hack knives"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which weapon does The Hawk use?",
        "answer": ["Naginata"]
    },
    {
        "question": " How Titan calls May after she has been kidnapped?",
        "answer": ["Justice"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who seeks help from Sensei during Old Wounds?",
        "answer": ["Prince"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which weapon covers most area of screen during attack?",
        "answer": ["Mowers"]
    }
]
